Franz Waxman Papers
Franz Waxman Papers
- Recordings
  - Professional recordings
    - Dinner for Harold L. Ickes by Hollywood Democratic Committee (Disc 1 of 5), 10/08/1944; waxman_0235; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Dinner for Harold L. Ickes by Hollywood Democratic Committee (Disc 2 of 5), 10/08/1944; waxman_0236; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Dinner for Harold L. Ickes by Hollywood Democratic Committee (Disc 3 of 5), 10/08/1944; waxman_0237; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Dinner for Harold L. Ickes by Hollywood Democratic Committee (Disc 4 of 5), 10/08/1944; waxman_0238; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Dinner for Harold L. Ickes by Hollywood Democratic Committee (Disc 5 of 5), 10/08/1944; waxman_0239; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Dirge, waxman_0623; Shellac disc
    - Divertimento, waxman_0867; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - Divinites Du Styx, waxman_0351; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Divinites Du Styx, Side A; Ahi Mon Fils, Side B
    - Djangology, waxman_0295; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Djangology, Side A; Ultrafox, Side B
    - Don Quixote (Disc 1 of 2), 10/22/1938; waxman_0201; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Don Quixote (Disc 2 of 2), 10/22/1938; waxman_0202; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Draußen in der Welt, waxman_0604; paper label on disc gives the German spelling of Waxman: Wachsmann; Shellac disc
      Draußen in der Welt, foxtrot aus dem Tonfilm: Die schonen Tage von Aranjuez, side A; GruB und KuB - Veronika, foxtrot aus dem gleichnamigen Tonfilm, side B
    - Ein Heldenleben, waxman_0899; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project 1979. Preservation re-recording of Ein Heldenleben by National Hollywood Symphony Orchestra? Franz Waxman acetate on aluminum 78 rpm. Re recorded by the Syracuse University Audio Archives.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Ein Heldenleben
    - Ein Heldenleben, Part 1, waxman_0973; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Ein Heldenleben Op. 40 (1 of 3), recorded 07/1948; waxman_0410; tone poem; symphony orchestra; Lacquer discs/acetates
      part 1, side A; part 4, side B
    - Ein Heldenleben Op. 40 (2 of 3), recorded 07/1948; waxman_0411; tone poem; symphony orchestra; Lacquer discs/acetates
      part 2, side A; part 5, side B
    - Ein Heldenleben Op. 40 (3 of 3), recorded 07/1948; waxman_0412; tone poem; symphony orchestra; Lacquer discs/acetates
      part 3, side A; part 6, side B
    - Eine Feste Burg, waxman_0296; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Eine Feste Burg, Side A; Russian Christmas Music, Side B
    - Elegie, waxman_0359; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Elegie, Side A; The Moon is High in the Sky, Side B
    - En Saga, waxman_0328; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - En Saga, waxman_0329; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Escape, 08/08/1940; waxman_0799; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Isoldes Liebestod
    - Estrella, waxman_0598; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Estrella, Side A; Valse Bluette, Side B
    - Euryanthe; Symphonie No. 2 Allegro, 02/12/1938; waxman_0045; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Everyone Says "I Love You", waxman_0301; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Everyone Says "I Love You", Side A; Butterflies in the Rain, Side B
    - Ezekiel Saw De Wheel, waxman_0319; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Ezekiel Saw De Wheel, Side A; Swing Low, Sweet Chariot, Side A; Keep Yo' Hand On The Plow, Side A, Hold On; Good News, Side B; Standin' in De Need of Prayer, Side B; Religion is a Fortune, Side B
    - Facade, waxman_0698; Lacquer discs/acetates
      William Walton
    - Facade, waxman_0699; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Noches Espagnol
    - The Fair at Sorochinsk, waxman_0271; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      The Fair at Sorochinsk, Side A; Golliwog's Cakewalk, Side B
    - The Fair at Sorochinsk, waxman_0272; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      A Hot Day in Little Russia
    - Fantaisie, waxman_0252; From Die Meistersinger of Nuremberg; commercial 78; Shellac disc
    - Fantasia, waxman_1094; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Farewell Message, 12/11/1936; waxman_0372; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Farewell Message, 12/11/1936; waxman_0373; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Fast and Furious (1 of 3), 3/10/1940; waxman_0080; Scenes 113, 114, 115, 116; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fast and Furious (2 of 3), 3/10/1940; waxman_0081; Scenes 117_1, 117_2, 118, 119_1, 119_2; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fast and Furious (3 of 3), 3/10/1940; waxman_0082; Scenes 120_1, 120_2; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Faust-Ballet, waxman_0388; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Variationa de Cleopatre, Side A; Les Troyennes, Side A; Variations du Miroir, Side B; Danse de Phryne, Side B
    - Faust - Nuit De Walpurgis, waxman_0391; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Faust - Nuit De Walpurgis, Side A; Prison Scene, Side A; Faust - Le Jour Va Luire, Side B
    - Faust - Nuit De Walpurgis, waxman_0392; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Dans las bruyeres, Side A; Jus-qu' aux premiers, Side B
    - Faust Ballet, waxman_0390; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Les Nubiennes, Side A; Danse Antique, Side A; Cleopatra and the Golden Cup, Side B
    - The Fawn and the Shepherdess, waxman_1023; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Felix Slatkin, 07/17/1962; waxman_0608; Lacquer discs/acetates
      My Geisha
    - Fior Di Loto, waxman_0764; Slow mod., Dal film Sayonara; Slow; film soundtrack; VinylDisc
      Fior Di Loto, side A; Come Prima, side B
    - First Rhapsody for Clarinet, waxman_0617; Shellac disc
      Beginning, Side A; Conclusion, Side B
    - First Symphony, waxman_1024; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Five String Banjo Tunes, waxman_0323; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Old Joe Clark, Side A; Chilly Winds, Side A; Cripple Creek, Side A; Cole Creek March, Side A; The Train, Side B
    - Flower Song from Carmen, aired 08/19/1947; waxman_0134B; Incomplete item digitization please skip; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - For Everything There Is A Season, Time Cycle (1 of 2), waxman_1079; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - For Everything There Is A Season, Time Cycle (2 of 2), waxman_1080; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Four Ostinatos, waxman_0678; instrumental music; Lacquer discs/acetates
      1. "Chimes" 2. Lullaby (on the name "Chalfa"), side A; Blue Arabesque, Little Boogie-Woogie, side B
    - Franco-Flemish chansons of the 15th Century, waxman_0626; Shellac disc
      Zwischen Berg, Side A; Pourrai-je Avoir, Side A; Le Jour s'endort, Side B; Ma Maitresse, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0637; French Course; Shellac disc
      5th Lesson, Side A; 6th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0638; French Course; Shellac disc
      7th Lesson, Side A; 8th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0639; French Course; Shellac disc
      11th Lesson, Side A; 12th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0640; French Course; Shellac disc
      9th Lesson, Side A; 10th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0641; French Course; Shellac disc
      19th Lesson, Side A; 20th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0642; French Course; Shellac disc
      13th Lesson, Side A; 14th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0643; French Course; Shellac disc
      15th Lesson, Side A; 16th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0644; French Course; Shellac disc
      17th Lesson, Side A; 18th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0645; French Course; Shellac disc
      21th Lesson, Side A; 22th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0646; French Course; Shellac disc
      23th Lesson, Side A; 24th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0647; French Course; Shellac disc
      25th Lesson, Side A; 26th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0648; French Course; Shellac disc
      27th Lesson, Side A; 28th Lesson, Side B
    - Francophone, waxman_0649; French Course; Shellac disc
      29th Lesson, Side A; 30th Lesson, Side B
    - Frankenstein, waxman_0533; Lacquer discs/acetates
      8. Reel, Side A; 9. Reel, Side B
    - Franz Waxman Biography at Hollywood Museum, 9/19/1964; waxman_0857; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Franz Waxman dubs from discs not from Belfer Audio Archives 1 of 2, waxman_0893; Dubs from discs not done at Belfer Audio Archive. Includes; Hudson-Terraplane Dealers and Earl Anthony Inc. "the Waikians" broadcast fragmented incomplete.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Bride of Frankenstein: pastorale, chase, menuetto, danse Macabre; Invisible Ray; Magnificent Obsession; The Waikikians
    - Franz Waxman dubs from discs not from Belfer Audio Archives 2 of 2, waxman_0892; Dubs from Discs not from Belfer Audio Archive.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Objective Burma; Tristan Fantasy; bride of Frankenstein creation part 1, creation part 2; Creation part 3 monster entrance.
    - Franz Waxman Interview with Bookspan, 1962; waxman_0856; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Free and Equal Blues, waxman_0324; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - French Dances of the 16th Century, waxman_0628; Shellac disc
      Bassedance, Side A; Toudion, Side A; Allemande, Side A; Pavane, Side B; Branle Simple, Side B; Branle Double, Side B; Branle de Bourgogne, Side B; Branle de Champagne, Side B
    - French Harpsichord Music in Couperin's Time, waxman_0630; Shellac disc
      Tombeau en forme d'Allemande, Side A; Le Fendant d'Oreille, Side B; La Noce d'Autell, Side B
    - French Operatic Arias, waxman_0618; Shellac disc
      The Damnation of Faust - Mephistopheles' Aie And Serenade, Side A; The Damnation of Faust - Song of the Flea, Side B; Romeo Et Juliette - Ballad of Queen Mab, Side B
    - French Suite, waxman_1074; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - French Suite For Orchestra, waxman_1072; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Fuer Franzchen, 1936; waxman_0808; Recitation in German; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Fur Franzchen
    - Fur'n Groschen Liebe, waxman_0571; Shellac disc
      Fur'n Groschen Liebe, Side A; Ach wie ist das Leben schon, Side B
    - Fur'n Groschen Liebe, waxman_0578; Shellac disc
      Fur'n Groschen Liebe, Side A; Halli - Halloh
    - Fury, waxman_0529; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Lynch - March
    - Fury, waxman_0530; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Ghoast's 2nd Version
    - Fury, waxman_0531; Lacquer discs/acetates
      At Joe's Home
    - Fury - Chattermusic, waxman_0528; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Chatter Music
    - Fury - Main Title, waxman_0527; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Main Title
    - The Fury and Next Time We Love, waxman_0882; part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-rerecording of Fury sound track from RCA Victor sample record pressing 78 rpm. Preservation re-recording of Next Time We Love sound track Cellutone acetate 33 1/3 rpm. Re-recorded at the Syracuse University Audio Archives 1979.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Fury main theme, At Joe's Home, the ghosts, chatter music; next time we love main theme, end title, liliom? (no good).
    - Furzo del Destino Overture; Concerto in G Minor (1 of 2), waxman_1047; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Furzo del Destino Overture; Concerto in G Minor (2 of 2), waxman_1048; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - German Dances; Five Pieces for String Orchestra, waxman_1026; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - German Municipal Music of the 17th Century, waxman_0627; Shellac disc
      Suite for Five Brass Instruments, Side A; Suite for Five Brass Instruments, Side B
    - German Organ Music of the 17th Century, waxman_0632; Shellac disc
      Choralle-Prelude: "Vater Unser", Side A; Chorale-Paraphrase: "Credo", side B
    - German Program in the Chamber Music Concerts, Adagio from Quartet No. 1, Opus 18, Violin Concerto in D, Don Quixote Suite, Cembalo Concerto in A, 4/20/1958; waxman_0987; Los Angeles County Museum; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - German Song, waxman_0825; soprano with piano accompaniment; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Gloria; Roger Wagner Chorale, waxman_1042; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - God is My Copilot, main title, waxman_0024; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Gone, waxman_0579; Shellac disc
      Gone, Side A; Love, What Are You Doing to My Heart, Side B
    - Gone, waxman_0581; Shellac disc
      Gone, Side A; I Love You From Coast to Coast, Side B
    - GONE - Fox Trot, waxman_0573; Shellac disc
      GONE - Fox Trot, Side A; I Love You From Coast to Coast - Fox Trot, Side B
    - GONE - Fox Trot, waxman_0574; Shellac disc
    - Great Americana Film Scores: The Kentuckian, 1977; waxman_0746; VinylDisc
      Side 1 The Kentuckian Suite Prelude; The Stagecoach; Victory; The Forest; Nocturne; Night Sounds; Scherzo; Miss Susie; The Rope; Finale; Side 2 Down To The Sea In Ships Main title & New Bedford Harbor; Hornpipe; Ol' Briny Jed; End Title; In Love & War Main Title; Requiem; Sunrise at Campobello Suite Main Title; Hyde Park; Ten Years Wiser & End Cast
    - Gruss Und Kuss - Veronika, waxman_0575; Shellac disc
      Gruss Und Kuss - Veronika, Side A; Die kleinen Madchen mit dem freuen Blick, Side B
    - gunsmoke dub, waxman_0909; gunsmoke radio due and a lot more stuff; dub of Allied Artists fascentation.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      gunsmoke dub; fascenation dub
    - Harold in Italy, part 1; Dr. Townsend Plan (1 of 3), 6/12/1944; 6/24/1944; 11/11/1944; waxman_0160; Concert broadcast. Concert at Symphony Hall, Boston; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 131)
      Side A: Harold in Italy, part 1; side B: Dr. Townsend Plan, Arizona #18 (The word transcription appears in opening remarks), not re-recorded, 1/1987, 2.5T, AW
    - Harold in Italy, part 2; [Dr. Townsend Plan?] (2 of 3), 11/11/1944; waxman_0161; Side A: concert broadcast.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 132)
      Side A, part 2; Side B: promo for Warner Brothers film "The Conspirators" (1944), director Jean Negulesco, music: "Siboney"; "I love you", Warner Brother's Studio Orchestra., “reference recording only” label with illegible markings in red crayon
    - Harold in Italy, part 3; Dr. Townsend Plan (3 of 3), 11/11/1944; waxman_0162; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 132)
      Side A: concert broadcast. Side B (no label): Dr. Francis E. Townsend talks on "State Townsend Employment and Retirement Mutual Insurance Plan; Proposition No. 11, H. R. 1649.
    - Haydn Concerto Grosso No. 1 in B Minor (4 of 4), waxman_0052; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Heifetz, waxman_0601; Lacquer discs/acetates
      3, Side A; Heifetz [Unknown Word], Side B
    - Heifetz, waxman_0602; Lacquer discs/acetates
      1, Side A; Heifetz [Unknown Word], Side B
    - Here Lies Love, waxman_0287; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Here Lies Love, Side A; Please, Side B
    - Hexpoda, waxman_0616; Shellac disc
    - Hidden Valley, waxman_0757; piano Duo with Orch. and Chorus; VinylDisc; running time 2:40; 2:50
      Hidden Valley, side A; Cimarron, side B
    - His Brother's Wife (1 of 10), waxman_0548; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - His Brother's Wife (10 of 10), waxman_0557; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Charley's Death
    - His Brother's Wife (2 of 10), waxman_0549; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Summer Holiday
    - His Brother's Wife (3 of 10), waxman_0550; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Can't We Fall in Love
    - His Brother's Wife (4 of 10), waxman_0551; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Guess Who? - A Balcony Scene
    - His Brother's Wife (5 of 10), waxman_0552; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Serum Montage
    - His Brother's Wife (6 of 10), waxman_0553; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - His Brother's Wife (7 of 10), waxman_0554; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Rita in Danger
    - His Brother's Wife (8 of 10), waxman_0555; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Prayer
    - His Brother's Wife (9 of 10), waxman_0556; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Rita
    - Hoffmanns Erzahlungen, waxman_0613; Shellac disc
      Hoffmanns Erzahlungen, Side A; Wiener Blut, Side B
    - Hollywood Bowl (1 of 5), 09/02/1946; waxman_0101; Lacquer discs/acetates
      National Anthem; Coralian Overture; Piano Concerto No. 1
    - Hollywood Bowl (2 of 5), 09/02/1946; waxman_0102; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Prelude to the Afternoon of a Faun; Piano Concerto No. 1
    - Hollywood Bowl (3 of 5), 09/02/1946; waxman_0103; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Florida Senator Claude Pepper; Frank Sinatra; Rhapsody in Blue
    - Hollywood Bowl (4 of 5), 09/02/1946; waxman_0104; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Florida Senator Claude Pepper; Frank Sinatra; Lonesome Train
    - Hollywood Bowl (5 of 5), 09/02/1946; waxman_0105; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Lonesome Train
    - Hollywood Bowl concert (1 of 4), 8/19/1947; waxman_0131; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Meistersinger Elegy; Romeo and Juliet part 1 beginning
    - Hollywood Bowl concert (2 of 4), 8/19/1947; waxman_0132; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Romeo and Juliet, conclusion; Lalo, Symphony Espagnol Movements 1 and 4
    - Hollywood Bowl concert (3 of 4), 8/19/1947; waxman_0133; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Zigeunerweisen; Symphony Espagnol Movement 5; Gayane and Hebrew Melody
    - Hollywood Bowl concert (4 of 4), 8/19/1947; waxman_0134; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Romanian Rhapsody; Bach Gavotte; Midsummer Night's Dream
    - Horn Concerto, waxman_0824; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Huck Finn; Good News, waxman_0224; MGM Theatre of the Air; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque, waxman_0676; Violin w/ Orchestra + Piano Accomp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Tristan Part 1, Side A; Tristan Part 2, Side B
    - Humoresque, waxman_0691; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Flight of the Bumblebee, Side A; Cesar Franc - Violin Sonata, Side B
    - Humoresque, waxman_0009; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque, Tristan, waxman_0064; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque: Carmen arrangement, waxman_0005; D2228; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque: Carmen arrangement, waxman_0011; C7157 #2 - 7564 1; C7157 #2 - 7564 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque: Carmen Fantasy arrangement, waxman_0008; D2245 (Record for im Warner); Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque: Concerto arrangement, waxman_0006; D2248 (added violin channel) 7367-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Humoresque: Romeo and Juliet arrangement, waxman_0010; 7963-3,4,5. NOT TRANSFERRED.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 130)
    - Humoresque: Symphonie Espagnole arrangement and Concerto Movment 1 arrangement, waxman_0007; D2247 (added violin channel) 7376-3-4-546; D2247 (added violin channel) 7566-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Hymnos Der Liebe, waxman_0171; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - I The Jury, waxman_0786; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Mary Bellany, Side A
    - I The Jury, 06/09/1953; waxman_0788; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - I. Research Period Gregorian Chant, waxman_0750; VinylDisc
      Introitus "Requiem Aeternam"; Kyrie; Oratio "Fidelium Deus omnium"; Epistola (1. Cor. 15, 51-57); Graduale "Requiem aeternam"; Tractus "Absolve, Domine"; Sequentia "Dies irae"; Evangelium; Offertorium "Domine Jesu Christe"; Praefatio Defunctorum; Sanctus; Pater noster; Agnus Dei; Communio "Lux Arterna"; Postcommunio "animabus quaesumus"; Requiescant in pace
    - I'd Be A Tree If You'd Be My Blossom, waxman_0291; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      I'd Be A Tree If You'd Be My Blossom, Side A; Messina Waltz, Side B
    - I'm Arricordo e Napule, waxman_0397; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      I'm Arricordo e Napule, Side A
    - I've Got You On My Mind, waxman_0299; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      I've Got You On My Mind, Side A; Who's Afraid of the Big, Bad Wolf?, Side B
    - I've Told Ev'ry Little Star, waxman_0284; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      I've Told Ev'ry Little Star, Side A; The Song is You, Side B
    - Il Segreto Di Susanna - Gioia, La Nube Leggera, waxman_0361; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Il Segreto Di Susanna - Gioia, La Nube Leggera, Side A; Manon - Adieu Notre Petite Table, Side B
    - In a Summer Garden, waxman_0331; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - In Our Time, waxman_0031; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - In Reference to Mr. Dewey (1 of 3), aired 11/07/1944; waxman_0714; Speech Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 1, side A; Part 2, side B
    - In Reference to Mr. Dewey (2 of 3), aired 11/07/1944; waxman_0715; Speech Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 3, side A; Part 4, side B
    - In Reference to Mr. Dewey (3 of 3), aired 11/07/1944; waxman_0716; Speech Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 5, side A
    - Interview with Franz Waxman, waxman_0978; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Interview with Naomi Reynolds, waxman_0686; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Interview with Naomi Reynolds; "Lonesome Train" performance announcement; Hollywood Bowl "Symphony of the Stars"
    - The Invisible Ray, 12/13/1935; waxman_0535; Lacquer discs/acetates
      The Accident, Side A; Love Scene, Side A; Poor Girl, Side A; The Storm, Side B; The Accident, Side B
    - The Invisible Ray, waxman_0883; part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-recordings of cellutone acetates 33 1/3 recorded on December 13, 1935. Re-recorded at the Syracuse University Audio Archives 1979.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Accident, Newspaper insert, love scene, Poor Girl; the Storm, The Accident.
    - The Jones Laughing Record (Introducing The Flight of the Bumble Bee), waxman_0375; Shellac disc
      The Jones Laughing Record (Introducing The Flight of the Bumble Bee), Side A;My Pretty Girl, Side B
    - Introduction and Rondo Capriccioso, waxman_0327; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Introduction and Rondo Capriccioso
    - Invitation to Music (Disc 1 of 2), 03/19/1947; waxman_0173; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Invitation to Music (Disc 2 of 2), 03/19/1947; waxman_0174; Orchestral Music; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Isaiah - Performance Reading, waxman_0785; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Isaiah - Performance Reading
    - L'isle Joyeuse, waxman_0395; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      L'isle Joyeuse, Side A; La Soiree Dans Grenade, Side B
    - Italian Ballades of the 14th Century, waxman_0631; Shellac disc
      Ita se n'era, Side A; lo son un pellegrin, Side A; Gloria in cielo, Side B; O celestial lume, Side B
    - Italian Symphonie, 02/05/1938; waxman_0043; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Je M'ennuie, waxman_0258; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Je M'ennuie, Side A; Assez, Side B
    - Je Nai Que Mon Coeur, waxman_0588; Shellac disc
      Je Nai Que Mon Coeur, Side A; Si Vous Saviez, Side B
    - Je Sais Que Vous Etes Jolie I, waxman_0255; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Je Said Que vous Etes Jolie I, Side A; Par Correspondance, Side B
    - Joan Of Arc (1 of 4), waxman_0001; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Joan of Arc, parts 1 and 3
    - Joan of Arc (2 of 4), waxman_0002; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Joan of Arc, Part 2 and Commentary
    - Joan of Arc (1 of 3), 01/04/1948; waxman_0012; Commentary and parts I to IV; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc (2 of 3), 01/04/1948; waxman_0013; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc (3 of 3), 01/04/1948; waxman_0014; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc (3 of 4), waxman_0003; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Joan of Arc, Part 4
    - Joan of Arc (4 of 4), waxman_0004; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Joan of Arc, part 5
    - Joan of Arc at the Stake, 1949; waxman_0108; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc at the Stake, 1949; waxman_0109; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc at the Stake, 1949; waxman_0110; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Joan of Arc at the Stake, 1949; waxman_0111; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Johannes Passion - Ruh't Wohl Ihr Heiligen Gebeine, waxman_0354; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Jonny Boy Variations, 08/08/1938; waxman_0661; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Jonny Boy Variations Played by Franz Waxman, Side A; Parody on Einst Lubish or an Evening at Ernt Lubisch's House, Side B